// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which element is used to include javascript in HTML?",
    answer: "<script>",
    options: [
      "&lt;javascript&gt;",
      "&lt;scripting&gt;",
      "&lt;script&gt;",
      "&lt;js&gt;"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following shows an alert dialogue box with a message?",
    answer: "alert()",
    options: [
      "alert()",
      "console.log()",
      "document.write()",
      "prompt()"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which is used to change the content of an HTML element?",
    answer: "innerHTML",
    options: [
      "innerWord",
      "innerDiv",
      "innerHTML",
      "change()"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following writes the browser's console?",
    answer: "console.log()",
    options: [
      "document.write()",
      "console.log()",
      "console.alert()",
      "console.write()"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following writes the browser's window?",
    answer: "document.write()",
    options: [
      "document.write()",
      "document.log()",
      "document.alert()",
      "console.write()"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Javascript is case-sensitive.",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "True", "False", "Maybe", "Sometimes"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which keyword is used to create a variable?",
    answer: "var",
    options: [
      "create", "const", "if", "var"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which one is used to write a multi-line comments in javascript?",
    answer: "/**/",
    options: [
      "//", "/**/", "&lt;!-- --&gt;", "#"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is the assignment operator",
    answer: "=",
    options: [
      "-", "+", "=&gt;", "="
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "var x = 12; var y = 'John'; total = x + y; console.log(total); What will be the result?",
    answer: "12John",
    options: [
      "Undefined", "12 John", "12John", "12 + John"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which one is used to write a single-line comments in javascript?",
    answer: "//",
    options: [
      "//", "/**/", "&lt;!-- --&gt;", "#"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Which of the following is the equality operator?",
    answer: "==",
    options: [
      "===", "==", "=", "!="
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Which of the following is the identity operator?",
    answer: "===",
    options: [
      "===", "==", "=", "!="
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which of the followwing returns false?",
    answer: "'2' === 2",
    options: [
      "2 == 2", "2 === 2", "&apos;2&apos; == 2", "&apos;2&apos; === 2"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which of the following is the LOGICAL OR operator?",
    answer: "||",
    options: [
      "!", "||", "&&", "none of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "What do you call a variable declared inside a function?",
    answer: "local variables",
    options: [
      "global variables", "local variables", "internal variables", "functional variables"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Which of the following is used to declare a function?",
    answer: "function",
    options: [
      "const", "var", "if...else", "function"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Which of the following is a collection of related data?",
    answer: "object",
    options: [
      "number", "string", "object", "none of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "In javascript,  what is a string?",
    answer: "a text",
    options: [
      "a number", "a text", "boolean", "none of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Which of the following is a number with decimal point?",
    answer: "floating point",
    options: [
      "floating point", "decimal", "integer", "fraction"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
